[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":30058,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":556706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6< /sub>, y ou start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8340,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":565048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1654,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":566704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4791,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":571496,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1582,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":573080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":9710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":582791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":584096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3695,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":587792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1255,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":589048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum i s 6 or b igger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":593343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1207,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":594551,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":597678,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":599103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":602854,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":41135,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":643990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perf orm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":5455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":649446,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1151,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":650598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5272,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":655871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":657175,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2568,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":659744,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1303,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":661048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":95026,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":756077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). S imilarly , 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":24009,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":780087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4639,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":784727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1152,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":785879,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse o f an ele ment is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["4","5"],"rt":4831,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":790710,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":791790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3615,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":795406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1015,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":796422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":798639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":799750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br />< br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4639,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":804390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5046,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":809438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":13439,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":822878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"W e have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":264566,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1087445,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element  which ca n make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":29077,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1116525,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":10526,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1127052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1132076,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry,  that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1759,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1133836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1138027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</ sub>, be cause 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1568,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1139595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1147435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":4335,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1151771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some ques tions ab out a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":9502,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1161275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1166155,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1167227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"-3","response_history":["-3"],"rt":13894,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1181122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4328,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1185451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1188826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4919,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1193746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1197987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. 4 + 1 equals 5, which is less than 9, and thus I used the actual number from addition.","response_history":["-4","-","-4. I took 4","5. 4 +1 ","5. 4 +1","5. 4 + 1 equals 5, which is less than 9, and thus I used the actual number from addition."],"rt":61078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1259066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +< sub>9</s ub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. 8 plus 4 equals 12, which is greater than 9. Subtracting 9 from 12 equals 3, the answer.","response_history":["3. 8 plus 4 equals 12, which is greater than 9. Subtracting 9 from 12 equals 3, the answer."],"rt":31279,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1290346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0. Adding zero to any number in +9 returns that number if the number is less than 9.","response_history":["0,","0. Adding se","0. Adding s","0. Adding zero to any number in =9 ","0. Adding zero to any number in =9","0. Adding zero to any number in =","0. Adding zero to any number in +9 returns that number if the number is less t han 9."],"rt":54104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1344451,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":10062,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1354514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1358594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get 0 as the final amount after backing out  the 9.","response_history":["6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get zer","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get ze","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get z","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get 0","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get 9, ","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get 9,","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get 9","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get ","6. If you add 6 to 3 in +9, you get 0 as the final amount after backing out the 9."],"rt":27687,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1386282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 10, 12, etc.","response_history":["No. 2 by itself can only ","Yes . 2 by t i","Yes. 2 by t","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. I t","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. I ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even u","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and 2","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd number ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the number ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the numbers ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the numb ers","Ye s. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the number","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the numbe","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the numb","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the num","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the nu","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when  the nr","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the n","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes over 10","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes over 1","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes over ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes over","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numb ers, and  covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes ove","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes ov","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes o","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 9, 10, ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system  when the  raw addition goes to 9, 10,","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 9, 10","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 9, 1","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 9, ","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 9,","Yes. 2 by itself can get to every number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 9","Yes. 2 by itself can ge t to eve ry number. It covers all single digit even numbers, and covers all odd numbers by the subtraction of 9 in the +9 system when the raw addition goes to 10, 12, etc."],"rt":144166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1530449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in +9 by itself. 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 are all impossible to generate with 3 by itself.","response_history":["No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in the system.","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in the system","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in ","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers i","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers ","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers","No. 3 cannot cover many number ","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in +9.","No. 3 cannot cover many  numbers  in +9 by itse.","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in +9 by itself. 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 are all impossible to generate with 3.","No. 3 cannot cover many numbers in +9 by itself. 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 are all impossible to generate with 3 by itself."],"rt":104110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1634560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5, and 6.","response_history":["No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itse.","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in =9","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in =","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The  only num bers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5, 6, ","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5, 6,","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5, 6","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5,  a","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5,  ","No. 5 leaves too many numbers uncovered if used by itself. The only numbers 5 covers in +9 are 1, 5, and 6."],"rt":98422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1732983,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only 3 and 6 can be generated.","response_history":["No. It lea s","No.  It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only 3, 6","No. It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only 3, ","No. It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only 3,","No. It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only 3","No. It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only ","No. It leaves too many uncovered numbers in +9. only 3 and 6 can be generated."],"rt":36743,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1769727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":7448,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1777176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"W hat is t he formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +n (n-1)","response_history":["1 +n (n-1)"],"rt":39517,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1816694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"The inverse of 1 in an +n formula is going to be one less than whatever n is.","response_history":["The inverse of 1 in an +n forum","The inverse of 1 in an +n foru","The inverse of 1 in an +n formula is going to be one less than whatever n is."],"rt":26263,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1842958,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know  if an e lement x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know. Maybe if the square of +n is lower than n, it is a generator?","response_history":["I don't know. Maybe if you sw","I don't know. Maybe if you s","I don't know. Maybe if you ","I don't know. Maybe if you","I don't know. Maybe if yo","I don't know. Maybe if y","I don't know. Maybe if the square of +n is lower than N,","I don't know. Maybe if the square of +n is lower than N","I don't know. Maybe if the square of +n is lower than n, it is a generator.","I don't know. Maybe if the square of +n is lower than n, it is a generator?"],"rt":48049,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1891007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":[" True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1897110,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1903247,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":19223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1922471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generat or under  +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multiple. ","response_history":["False. I think if it is a divisor","False. I think if it ","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes n ","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes n","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under =9, an","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under =9, a","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under =9, ","False. I think if  it is a  divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under =9,","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under =9","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under =","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multple. ","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multple.","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multple","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multpl"," False. I  think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multp","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multiple. 4 is a generator under +6,an","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multiple. 4 is a generator under +6,a","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multiple. 4 is a generator under +6, and the ","False. I think if it is a divisor of a multiple of n, that this makes x a generator. For instance, 3 is a generator under +9, and is a divisor of a multiple. "],"rt":86333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2008805,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":8358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2017165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes, but it can change with whether n is and x are even or odd numbers.","response_history":["Always, ","Always,","Always","Alway","Alwa","Alw","Al","A","Sometimes, but it can change with the ","Sometimes, but it can change with the","Sometimes, but it can cha nge with  th","Sometimes, but it can change with t","Sometimes, but it can change with whether n is e","Sometimes, but it can change with whether n is and x are even or odd.","Sometimes, but it can change with whether n is and x are even or odd numbers."],"rt":170767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2187933,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":8487,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2196421,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1863,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2198285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"37","response_history":["37"],"rt":6118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2204404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2207396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanc ed, plea se list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"college algebra I","response_history":["college algre","college algr","college algebra I"],"rt":14677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2222075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2226875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":" multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2230115,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":4247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2234364,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - s omewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2743,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2237107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2240379,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2242619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a  child.) ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2247187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2250995,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It was an interesting hit with a bell curve that felt like a cliff!","response_history":["It was interesting, although it also ","It was inte","It was int","It was in","It was i","It was an interesting hit with a bell curve that felt like a l","It was an interesting hit with a bell curve that felt like  a cliff! "],"rt":21191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2272187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]